let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Find the mode of the given data: 3,4,6,2,3,5,1,3,5,4,1,3,5,1,5,3,2,3,3,6 ",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "x + 14 = 24. Find the value of <b> x </b>",
    answer: "10",
    options: [
      "10",
      "11",
      "9",
      "13"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "8y = 56. Find the value of <b> y </b>",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "7",
      "8",
      "6",
      "9"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "-22 = 7y + 6. Find the value of <b> y </b>",
    answer: "-4",
    options: [
      "4",
      "-4",
      "-5",
      "3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "-8x = 72. Find the value of <b> x </b>",
    answer: "-9",
    options: [
      "9",
      "-9",
      "6",
      "10"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A dice is thrown.Find the probability of getting an even number?",
    answer: "1/2",
    options: [
      "1/2",
      "2/3",
      "4/5",
      "5/6"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Find the mode of the given data: 20,14,18,9,11,9,5,14,13.",
    answer: "14 and 9",
    options: [
      "14 and 9",
      "13 and 9",
      "18 and 11",
      "20 and 9"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Find the mean of the given data: 50,46,49,55,50,51,56",
    answer: "51",
    options: [
      "50",
      "61",
      "52",
      "51"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Find the range if the given data: 100,94,87,67,90,92,101,107 and 90.",
    answer: "40",
    options: [
      "40",
      "50",
      "55",
      "60"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the probability of getting heads when coin is tossed? ",
    answer: "1/2",
    options: [
      "3/5",
      "1/4",
      "1/3",
      "1/2"
    ]
  },



];